[{"key": "text1675268041", "inputs": [{"text": "The 22nd annual IEEE Wireless and Microwave Technology Conference, WAMICON 2022, will be held in Clearwater Beach, Florida, on April 27-28, 2022. The conference will address up-to-date multidisciplinary research needs and interdisciplinary aspects of wireless and RF technology. The central theme of WAMICON 2022 is \"Waves Through Air and Space.\" We welcome submissions on all aspects of related technologies, including antennas, passive and active circuits, communication theory, and system concepts."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "annual", "start": 9, "end": 15, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7073d24a-a24b-11ed-9f5d-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "IEEE", "start": 16, "end": 20, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70743350-a24b-11ed-980f-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Clearwater Beach", "start": 97, "end": 113, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "707480e1-a24b-11ed-861a-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Florida", "start": 115, "end": 122, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "7074c317-a24b-11ed-a691-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "April 27-28, 2022", "start": 127, "end": 144, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "70750fad-a24b-11ed-aa37-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268042", "inputs": [{"text": "The walk down the aisle is one of the more special and memorable moments of the wedding day, and trust us, it goes by quickly. Capture it all on camera from your vantage point by asking your florist to save a spot in your bridal bouquet for a small camera. (Any mini camera similar to a GoPro will work to record your entrance.) This way you'll get to see everything from the look on your guests' faces to the parental handoff (if that's what you're doing) to your vows in an up-close and personal way."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "the wedding", "start": 76, "end": 87, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "70755ec2-a24b-11ed-82f3-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "GoPro", "start": 287, "end": 292, "label_custom_id": "PRODUCT", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6d", "label_text": "PRODUCT", "uuid": "7075a2eb-a24b-11ed-943e-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268043", "inputs": [{"text": "Melbourne’s biggest gastronomic celebration, the Melbourne Food and Wine Festival, marks its 28th year in 2020. Melbourne’s home of fresh food, the Queen Victoria Market, is playing host to the festival with 10 days of dinners, parties, talks, demonstrations and free events for the whole family.  All day and into the night the Market will be a magnet for food-loving Melburnians and visitors, celebrating everything that makes our city delicious, from Sichuan to spaghetti, plants to passionate people."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "Melbourne", "start": 0, "end": 9, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "70760f5b-a24b-11ed-8ab3-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "its 28th year", "start": 89, "end": 102, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "70766368-a24b-11ed-95a9-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "2020", "start": 106, "end": 110, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7076b51f-a24b-11ed-a55e-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Melbourne", "start": 112, "end": 121, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "7076f2b9-a24b-11ed-8d06-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "the Queen Victoria Market", "start": 144, "end": 169, "label_custom_id": "FACILITY", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf69", "label_text": "FACILITY", "uuid": "707745eb-a24b-11ed-830d-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "10 days", "start": 208, "end": 215, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7077937b-a24b-11ed-8159-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "the night", "start": 315, "end": 324, "label_custom_id": "TIME", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf54", "label_text": "TIME", "uuid": "707807e0-a24b-11ed-a726-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Market", "start": 329, "end": 335, "label_custom_id": "FACILITY", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf69", "label_text": "FACILITY", "uuid": "7078557e-a24b-11ed-bf23-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268044", "inputs": [{"text": "SPIE Remote Sensing is Europe's largest international forum for remote sensing. The event offers comprehensive coverage of remote sensing including next-generation satellites, SAR image analysis, LADAR technologies and more. The conference covers the latest enabling technologies and applications for signal and image processing. Remote Sensing is co-located with Security + Defence. The SPIE Remote Sensing will take place on 4 days from Monday, 05. September to Thursday, 08. September 2022 in Berlin."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "SPIE Remote Sensing", "start": 0, "end": 19, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7078be31-a24b-11ed-8451-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Europe", "start": 23, "end": 29, "label_custom_id": "NON_GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf68", "label_text": "NON_GPE", "uuid": "707919ad-a24b-11ed-820c-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Remote Sensing", "start": 330, "end": 344, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70795314-a24b-11ed-9f2b-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Security + Defence", "start": 364, "end": 382, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7079a0b8-a24b-11ed-960b-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "The SPIE Remote Sensing", "start": 384, "end": 407, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7079dbb8-a24b-11ed-b85b-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "4 days", "start": 427, "end": 433, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "707a15ee-a24b-11ed-b73d-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Monday, 05. September to Thursday, 08. September 2022", "start": 439, "end": 492, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "707a5020-a24b-11ed-af62-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Berlin", "start": 496, "end": 502, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "707a8fe3-a24b-11ed-87cc-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268045", "inputs": [{"text": "Producing Your First Audiobook. November 16, 2021 @ 1:00 pm - 2:00 pm EST. Producing Your First Audiobook, with Sherry Ward of Square Tree Publishing- This free workshop will be a detailed look at the processes and requirements for creating an audiobook of your written work. We will give you the step-by-step process and the affordable equipment you will need in order to produce a professional sounding audiobook. Register Here Today! https://us02web.zoom.us/webinar/register/WN_3kiKktzaQwynTYyjn4GIdQ"}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "November 16, 2021", "start": 32, "end": 49, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "707af0f3-a24b-11ed-8e56-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "1:00 pm - 2:00 pm EST", "start": 52, "end": 73, "label_custom_id": "TIME", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf54", "label_text": "TIME", "uuid": "707b3e97-a24b-11ed-8694-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Sherry Ward", "start": 112, "end": 123, "label_custom_id": "PERSON", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6b", "label_text": "PERSON", "uuid": "707b78b5-a24b-11ed-99b8-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Square Tree Publishing-", "start": 127, "end": 150, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "707bc653-a24b-11ed-a60b-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Today", "start": 430, "end": 435, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "707c01cf-a24b-11ed-82d6-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268046", "inputs": [{"text": "The Franchise Expo - Toronto is North America's largest circuit of successful and proven events. National Event Management's Franchise Shows are unquestionably the largest and best-attended regional shows in North America. This show is your opportunity to meet face to face with thousands of potential franchisees or business partners eager to own their own business. See the most successful franchises + brand new opportunities from every industry. Save Hundreds of Hours of Research Time! Free Seminars!"}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "Toronto", "start": 21, "end": 28, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "707c5611-a24b-11ed-81a4-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "North America's", "start": 32, "end": 47, "label_custom_id": "NON_GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf68", "label_text": "NON_GPE", "uuid": "707ca3aa-a24b-11ed-af9b-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "National Event Management's", "start": 97, "end": 124, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "707cf153-a24b-11ed-8188-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "North America", "start": 208, "end": 221, "label_custom_id": "NON_GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf68", "label_text": "NON_GPE", "uuid": "707d2b7f-a24b-11ed-a90c-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Hundreds of Hours", "start": 455, "end": 472, "label_custom_id": "TIME", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf54", "label_text": "TIME", "uuid": "707d69f9-a24b-11ed-be01-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268047", "inputs": [{"text": "Mount Vernon Band Boosters Pork Chop & Chicken Jazz Dinner WHERE: First United Methodist Church, 601 Main St, Mt Vernon, IN DATE: Saturday April 2nd, 2022 TIME: 4:30 to 7:30 PM. COST: Carry Out Pork or Chicken $14.00, Children’s Hotdog Meal $5.00. The Jazz Band will be play throughout the evening for your entertainment. Dinner includes: Smoked Pork Chop OR Half Chicken, Choice of 2 sides, Roll, Dessert and Drink for Dine-In orders. Carry Out available. All orders must be prepaid by Friday, March 25th."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "Mount Vernon Band", "start": 0, "end": 17, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "707db794-a24b-11ed-a9d3-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "First United Methodist Church", "start": 66, "end": 95, "label_custom_id": "FACILITY", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf69", "label_text": "FACILITY", "uuid": "707df1c9-a24b-11ed-a32d-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "601 Main St", "start": 97, "end": 108, "label_custom_id": "FACILITY", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf69", "label_text": "FACILITY", "uuid": "707e2f4b-a24b-11ed-9a38-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Mt Vernon", "start": 110, "end": 119, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "707e6b86-a24b-11ed-9d81-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Saturday April 2nd, 2022", "start": 130, "end": 154, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "707ea92b-a24b-11ed-801e-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "4:30 to 7:30 PM", "start": 161, "end": 176, "label_custom_id": "TIME", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf54", "label_text": "TIME", "uuid": "707ef6c9-a24b-11ed-a185-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "14.00", "start": 211, "end": 216, "label_custom_id": "CURRENCY", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf5b", "label_text": "CURRENCY", "uuid": "707f4462-a24b-11ed-a4a9-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "5.00", "start": 242, "end": 246, "label_custom_id": "CURRENCY", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf5b", "label_text": "CURRENCY", "uuid": "707f7e9e-a24b-11ed-a31b-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "The Jazz Band", "start": 248, "end": 261, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "707fcc31-a24b-11ed-839c-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Friday, March 25th", "start": 487, "end": 505, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "707ff6d6-a24b-11ed-a02a-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268048", "inputs": [{"text": "GaN devices, such as discrete GaNFETs and integrated circuits entirely made of GaN technology, are widely being adopted across different applications and are becoming well recognized in the power electronics industry. In the workshop, the basics of the GaN technology will be presented, to share basic knowledge and to depict the main difference vs. MOSFET technology. During the talks in the workshop, the GaN approach and its related advantages will be presented for dc-dc converters, motors, and Lidars."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "Lidars", "start": 499, "end": 505, "label_custom_id": "PRODUCT", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6d", "label_text": "PRODUCT", "uuid": "7080446a-a24b-11ed-baa1-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268049", "inputs": [{"text": "Thirty eighth IEEE International Conference on Software Maintenance and Evolution => ICSME 2022. Hosted in – Atlantica Miramare Beach Hotel, Limassol, Cyprus. 03 - 07 October 2022. The International Conference on Software Maintenance and Evolution is the ultimate global discussion board for researchers and practitioners from academia, industry, and authorities to present, discuss, and debate the maximum latest ideas, experiences, and demanding situations in software program preservation and evolution."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "2022", "start": 91, "end": 95, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7080856f-a24b-11ed-bd47-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Atlantica Miramare Beach Hotel", "start": 109, "end": 139, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7080d306-a24b-11ed-b27e-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Limassol", "start": 141, "end": 149, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "70810d3a-a24b-11ed-95b7-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Cyprus", "start": 151, "end": 157, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "70816e3c-a24b-11ed-bd23-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "03 - 07 October 2022", "start": 159, "end": 179, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7081b743-a24b-11ed-b141-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268050", "inputs": [{"text": "SPIE Security + Defence is Europe's top security and defence exhibition. It attracts leaders from the security and defence sector from both Europe and North America to share topics and technology developments. Areas of interest range from detectors and sensors to lasers and imaging equipment for the security and defence community. The SPIE Security + Defence will take place on 2 days from Tuesday, 06. September to Wednesday, 07. September 2022 in Berlin. Trade fair for security and defence technology."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "Europe", "start": 27, "end": 33, "label_custom_id": "NON_GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf68", "label_text": "NON_GPE", "uuid": "7081ff86-a24b-11ed-a950-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Europe", "start": 140, "end": 146, "label_custom_id": "NON_GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf68", "label_text": "NON_GPE", "uuid": "70823d82-a24b-11ed-a2b5-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "North America", "start": 151, "end": 164, "label_custom_id": "NON_GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf68", "label_text": "NON_GPE", "uuid": "708277b8-a24b-11ed-834c-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "2 days", "start": 380, "end": 386, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7082b28f-a24b-11ed-969e-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Tuesday, 06. September to Wednesday, 07. September 2022", "start": 392, "end": 447, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7082ed13-a24b-11ed-91d9-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Berlin", "start": 451, "end": 457, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "708313e1-a24b-11ed-bed5-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268051", "inputs": [{"text": "The Venice Commission organized a coordination assembly with the representatives from the country establishments of Uzbekistan, particularly from the Supreme Court, the Prosecutor General, the National Centre for Human Rights, Oliy Majlis, the Anti-Corruption corporation and the Embassy of the Republic of Uzbekistan in Brussels. The assembly served to speak about in element concrete proposals for co-operation with the Venice Commission with inside the framework of the Central Asia Rule of Law Programme."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "The Venice Commission", "start": 0, "end": 21, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "708363b0-a24b-11ed-b24a-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Uzbekistan", "start": 116, "end": 126, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "7083a72d-a24b-11ed-95a7-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "the Supreme Court", "start": 146, "end": 163, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7083f4b9-a24b-11ed-8da8-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "the National Centre for Human Rights", "start": 189, "end": 225, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70843a86-a24b-11ed-8dd7-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Oliy Majlis", "start": 227, "end": 238, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70847e7f-a24b-11ed-82e9-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "the Anti-Corruption corporation", "start": 240, "end": 271, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7084bea1-a24b-11ed-829b-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "the Embassy of the Republic of Uzbekistan", "start": 276, "end": 317, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70850c3a-a24b-11ed-914d-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Brussels", "start": 321, "end": 329, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "708532fd-a24b-11ed-a4e7-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "the Venice Commission", "start": 418, "end": 439, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70856d35-a24b-11ed-8a5f-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "the Central Asia Rule of Law Programme", "start": 469, "end": 507, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7085a765-a24b-11ed-bee5-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268052", "inputs": [{"text": "If you could be a family member for a day, who would you be, and what would you do to help them out? I would be my wife and I would insist that my husband got the Meecum Motorcycle Auction in Vegas next January. There, I would also insist that he buy the vintage motorcycle of his choice, probably a Harley-Davidson, but possibly a Triumph, Norton, or even a Kawasaki or Honda. How would this help her out? Happy husband, happy...I can't think of anything that rhymes with husband. But you get me, don't you?"}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "a day", "start": 36, "end": 41, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7085f359-a24b-11ed-bb6b-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Vegas", "start": 192, "end": 197, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "708641ae-a24b-11ed-a7d9-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "next January", "start": 198, "end": 210, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "70867be4-a24b-11ed-b312-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Harley-Davidson", "start": 300, "end": 315, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7086b786-a24b-11ed-89e7-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Triumph", "start": 332, "end": 339, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7086ecd0-a24b-11ed-91cb-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Norton", "start": 341, "end": 347, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70872701-a24b-11ed-8227-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Kawasaki", "start": 359, "end": 367, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70874a1f-a24b-11ed-aeaa-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Honda", "start": 371, "end": 376, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "708782b0-a24b-11ed-a207-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268053", "inputs": [{"text": "Back to School Shopping Sales : That time of the year is back! Whether you’re packing your kids lunches for elementary school, or buying things to set up your new dorm room for college, online shopping is gonna be your best friend for finding the best deals. August through September you will see tax free weekends, BOGO’s, and so many discounts it’ll feel a little more like your birthday than boring old school shopping! Here at US Unlocked we have put together your back to school shopping survival guide."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "That time of the year", "start": 32, "end": 53, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7087bda9-a24b-11ed-820e-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "August through September", "start": 259, "end": 283, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "708805fe-a24b-11ed-bec9-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "weekends", "start": 306, "end": 314, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "70885e81-a24b-11ed-8458-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "US Unlocked", "start": 431, "end": 442, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70889975-a24b-11ed-b2dd-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268054", "inputs": [{"text": "Join us in summer 2022 for two days to reinforce your AWS security posture. Discover how AWS is innovating in the world of cloud security, and then hone your technical skills in expert-led interactive sessions. You’ll hear the latest from industry-leading speakers in security, compliance, identity, and privacy and meet fellow security professionals at our fun events. Stay tuned for more updates and information about attending re:Inforce 2022. JULY 26 – 27, 2022 | BOSTON, MA. FULL CONFERENCE PASS: $1,099."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "summer 2022", "start": 11, "end": 22, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7088d751-a24b-11ed-8ad3-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "two days", "start": 27, "end": 35, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "70890ebe-a24b-11ed-8636-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "AWS", "start": 54, "end": 57, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70894f31-a24b-11ed-9ec7-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "AWS", "start": 89, "end": 92, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7089984c-a24b-11ed-a7f3-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Inforce", "start": 433, "end": 440, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7089bddc-a24b-11ed-bf58-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "2022", "start": 441, "end": 445, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7089f813-a24b-11ed-aa7f-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "JULY 26 – 27, 2022", "start": 447, "end": 465, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "708a45b0-a24b-11ed-9d6f-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "BOSTON", "start": 468, "end": 474, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "708a9348-a24b-11ed-a036-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "MA", "start": 476, "end": 478, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "708ae0e3-a24b-11ed-8a7a-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "1,099", "start": 503, "end": 508, "label_custom_id": "CURRENCY", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf5b", "label_text": "CURRENCY", "uuid": "708b30dd-a24b-11ed-a60c-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268055", "inputs": [{"text": "The 11th edition of the National Street Food Festival is being held at JLN Stadium, New Delhi from 25 to 29 Dec. The National Association of Street Vendors of India (NASVI) and food regulator FSSAI (Food Safety and Standards Authority of India) are jointly organising the event. The theme of the festival is ‘Healthier Diets’. It will feature street vendors from over 26 states displaying over 500 regional cuisines. The idea is to focus various initiatives of FSSAI around healthy eating through gamification."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "JLN Stadium", "start": 71, "end": 82, "label_custom_id": "FACILITY", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf69", "label_text": "FACILITY", "uuid": "708b7e7f-a24b-11ed-b2cc-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "New Delhi", "start": 84, "end": 93, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "708bb8ab-a24b-11ed-b9c0-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "25 to 29 Dec.", "start": 99, "end": 112, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "708bf2e2-a24b-11ed-8a2a-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "The National Association of Street Vendors of India", "start": 113, "end": 164, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "708c4082-a24b-11ed-a69d-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "NASVI", "start": 166, "end": 171, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "708ca17c-a24b-11ed-b5c0-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "FSSAI", "start": 192, "end": 197, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "708cef1c-a24b-11ed-b13e-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Food Safety and Standards Authority of India", "start": 199, "end": 243, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "708d5017-a24b-11ed-b1ef-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "FSSAI", "start": 461, "end": 466, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "708d8a4d-a24b-11ed-b527-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268056", "inputs": [{"text": "About IEEE VISSOFT 2022 – The tenth IEEE Working Conference on Software Visualization (VISSOFT 2022) builds upon the fulfillment of the preceding nine versions of VISSOFT, which in flip observed after six versions of the IEEE International Workshop on Visualizing Software for Understanding and Analysis (VISSOFT) and five versions of the ACM Symposium on Software Visualization (SOFTVIS). In 2022, VISSOFT will take region and be co-positioned with ICSME. Conference Date: October 2-3, 2022, Limassol, Cyprus."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "IEEE", "start": 6, "end": 10, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "708deb52-a24b-11ed-8f85-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "2022", "start": 19, "end": 23, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "708e38ed-a24b-11ed-97df-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "IEEE Working Conference on Software Visualization", "start": 36, "end": 85, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "708e8686-a24b-11ed-98a1-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "2022", "start": 95, "end": 99, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "708ed420-a24b-11ed-b73f-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "2022", "start": 393, "end": 397, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "708f0e61-a24b-11ed-816d-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "VISSOFT", "start": 399, "end": 406, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "708f5bf0-a24b-11ed-bde4-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "ICSME", "start": 450, "end": 455, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "708fa98b-a24b-11ed-8dfb-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "October 2-3, 2022", "start": 474, "end": 491, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "708fe3bd-a24b-11ed-b23c-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Limassol", "start": 493, "end": 501, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "70901df4-a24b-11ed-8c69-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Cyprus", "start": 503, "end": 509, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "709062f2-a24b-11ed-a28b-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268057", "inputs": [{"text": "The 2022 College and Career Fair is scheduled for Thursday, March 30, from 5:30 p.m. to 7:30 p.m. This event is for businesses who would like to answer questions from students and parents about the skills needed to fill positions you may have now or in the future.  College representatives will also be on hand to talk to students about career paths and classes that may benefit them in pursuit of their career choice.  This is our best chance to get local, skilled employees to fill those hard to fill positions."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "2022", "start": 4, "end": 8, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7090b08e-a24b-11ed-a2a2-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Thursday, March 30", "start": 50, "end": 68, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7090e9dc-a24b-11ed-bbf1-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "5:30 p.m. to 7:30 p.m.", "start": 75, "end": 97, "label_custom_id": "TIME", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf54", "label_text": "TIME", "uuid": "7091240e-a24b-11ed-aa92-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268058", "inputs": [{"text": "The 15th Asia Joint Conference on Information Security (AsiaJCIS 2020) will be held in Taipei, Taiwan on August 20 through 21, 2020. The focus of this conference is on the technical and practical aspects of the security applications. The conference will serve as a forum to present new results from the academic research community as well as from the industry. Original papers are solicited for submission to AsiaJCIS. In addition, several distinguished security experts will be invited to give technical talks."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "2020", "start": 65, "end": 69, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "70915fa5-a24b-11ed-af86-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Taipei", "start": 87, "end": 93, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "709193d1-a24b-11ed-88d1-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Taiwan", "start": 95, "end": 101, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "7091e170-a24b-11ed-870f-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "August 20 through 21, 2020", "start": 105, "end": 131, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "70921ba8-a24b-11ed-b69d-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "AsiaJCIS", "start": 409, "end": 417, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70926943-a24b-11ed-9411-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268059", "inputs": [{"text": "World Computer Day is a global celebration of the positive benefits of computers held on February 15th, each year. February 15th was chosen as it was the start-up date for the ENIAC; the world's first all electronic, programmable computer in 1946. World Computer Day is an annual celebration of computing and the people who make IT happen. There's much to celebrate this year for World Computer Day, but nothing more important than the celebration of the revolutionary 6502 chip; the chip that changed the world!"}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "February 15th,", "start": 89, "end": 103, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7092b6e1-a24b-11ed-aab5-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "each year", "start": 104, "end": 113, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7092f10f-a24b-11ed-b73c-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "February 15th", "start": 115, "end": 128, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "70932fee-a24b-11ed-bcaa-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "ENIAC", "start": 176, "end": 181, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70936be8-a24b-11ed-b5f9-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "1946", "start": 242, "end": 246, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7093b9a0-a24b-11ed-bcd4-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "annual", "start": 273, "end": 279, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "709407f5-a24b-11ed-ab41-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "this year", "start": 366, "end": 375, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "70943ce4-a24b-11ed-8a6a-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "6502", "start": 469, "end": 473, "label_custom_id": "PRODUCT", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6d", "label_text": "PRODUCT", "uuid": "70948a7f-a24b-11ed-96fc-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268060", "inputs": [{"text": "After 1 billion vaccinations with Biontech Pfizer, we now have the numbers to pinpoint the risks of the vaccination vs Covid-19 pandemic. There are not many severe side-effects with the Biontech vaccine, except for Myocarditis, which is the most frequently occuring severe side-effect. Let us have a look exactly at the numbers. Myocarditis- Myocardities is a heart inflammation, which has a high chance of occuring after any bacterial, viral infection or any other kinds of stimulation of the immune system."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "Biontech Pfizer", "start": 34, "end": 49, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7094c1b6-a24b-11ed-a12d-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Biontech", "start": 186, "end": 194, "label_custom_id": "PRODUCT", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6d", "label_text": "PRODUCT", "uuid": "7094f997-a24b-11ed-9c7d-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268061", "inputs": [{"text": "ICLS is being organized by Researchfora. The aim of the conference is to provide the platform for Students, Researchers and Academicians to share the knowledge and ideas in the recent trends in the field of Law and Society. ICLS will provide an excellent international forum for sharing knowledge and a result in Law and Society. The aim of the Conference is to provide a platform to the researchers and practitioners from both academia as well as industry to meet the share cutting-edge development in the field."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "ICLS", "start": 0, "end": 4, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "709546a5-a24b-11ed-b2bf-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Researchfora", "start": 27, "end": 39, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "709580d3-a24b-11ed-b26b-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "ICLS", "start": 224, "end": 228, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7095ce8b-a24b-11ed-b359-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268062", "inputs": [{"text": "Do you get a better deal on boats at a boat show? If the boat on display at the boat show is most appealing and meets one’s desires, then one could get a good deal. Firstly, the boat maker does not have to ship the boat to the next show or back to the yard; the new owner’s boat slip will do just fine. And secondly, the deal will be on all of the “show” items that have been put into the boat. Don’t have a boat slip and the new boat is not a trailerable, then it would not matter how much of a deal one can get."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": []}]}, {"key": "text1675268063", "inputs": [{"text": "The Oil Sands Trade Show in Fort McMurray is one of the leading trade fairs for oil sands in the world. At the fair numerous exhibitors present information about the second-largest known oil reserve. Visitors come together at this event to find out about the latest technologies and products for the industry. Moreover, sustainable solutions for environmental protection are discussed. The Oil Sands Trade Show will take place on 3 days from Wednesday, 14. September to Friday, 16. September 2022 in Fort McMurray."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "Fort McMurray", "start": 28, "end": 41, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "70962258-a24b-11ed-b170-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "3 days", "start": 430, "end": 436, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "70965d6f-a24b-11ed-93f9-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Wednesday, 14. September to Friday, 16. September 2022", "start": 442, "end": 496, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7096a155-a24b-11ed-9398-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Fort McMurray", "start": 500, "end": 513, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "7096dad9-a24b-11ed-9c21-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268064", "inputs": [{"text": "On March 25-26, 2022, the Atlantic Council’s Cyber Statecraft Initiative will host its 9th annual Cyber 9/12 Strategy Challenge in Washington, DC. The event can be hung on the Zoom platform as opposed to our common in-character opposition. Except that it will likely be held remotely, the schedule and shape can be in large part same to preceding Cyber 9/12 Challenges. Plenary classes can be live-streamed via Zoom from the Atlantic Council’s offices, and opposition rounds will take location through Zoom meetings."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "March 25-26, 2022", "start": 3, "end": 20, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "70972879-a24b-11ed-acfc-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "the Atlantic Council’s", "start": 22, "end": 44, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70976837-a24b-11ed-ba1c-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Cyber Statecraft Initiative", "start": 45, "end": 72, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7097abb7-a24b-11ed-a51f-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "annual", "start": 91, "end": 97, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "7097e5ec-a24b-11ed-8d56-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Washington", "start": 131, "end": 141, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "70982020-a24b-11ed-b400-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "DC", "start": 143, "end": 145, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "70985987-a24b-11ed-860a-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Zoom", "start": 176, "end": 180, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7098b2cd-a24b-11ed-b08f-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Zoom", "start": 411, "end": 415, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70991194-a24b-11ed-a73f-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "the Atlantic Council’s", "start": 421, "end": 443, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70994df4-a24b-11ed-be8e-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Zoom", "start": 502, "end": 506, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70998825-a24b-11ed-adc7-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268065", "inputs": [{"text": "NHSLMA Spring Conference is a professional organization representing school library media specialists and paraprofessionals. We are an affiliate of the American Association of School Librarians and the New England School Library Association. We provide our members with a forum for the exchange of ideas and with opportunities for professional growth through publications, conferences, and professional development workshops.  NHSLMA Spring Conference: 31 Mar - 01 Apr 2022Add Grappone Conference Center, Concord, USA."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "NHSLMA Spring Conference", "start": 0, "end": 24, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "7099d5c0-a24b-11ed-9311-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "the American Association of School Librarians", "start": 148, "end": 193, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "709a235d-a24b-11ed-a338-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "the New England School Library Association", "start": 198, "end": 240, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "709a622d-a24b-11ed-a18e-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "NHSLMA Spring Conference", "start": 427, "end": 451, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "709aa036-a24b-11ed-ab4c-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "31 Mar - 01 Apr 2022Add", "start": 453, "end": 476, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "709add45-a24b-11ed-b8d1-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Grappone Conference Center", "start": 477, "end": 503, "label_custom_id": "FACILITY", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf69", "label_text": "FACILITY", "uuid": "709b177c-a24b-11ed-b61d-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Concord", "start": 505, "end": 512, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "709b42d5-a24b-11ed-b2d4-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "USA", "start": 514, "end": 517, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "709b793a-a24b-11ed-adb3-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268066", "inputs": [{"text": "So, even when me and my husband decided not to spend too much on our wedding, only my side ended up spending more than Rs.15 lakhs (which includes jewellery gifted by my parents and around 10 lakhs of my own savings).The major chunk went to the 2 venues where my wedding and reception, hosted by my parents, were held. (His family hosted another reception at their place).In India, no matter how resolute one is, parents always want to make your wedding memorable, which means a number of functions and lot of guests."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "Rs.15 lakhs", "start": 119, "end": 130, "label_custom_id": "CURRENCY", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf5b", "label_text": "CURRENCY", "uuid": "709bb58b-a24b-11ed-a99f-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "around 10 lakhs", "start": 182, "end": 197, "label_custom_id": "CURRENCY", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf5b", "label_text": "CURRENCY", "uuid": "709c0326-a24b-11ed-a977-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "India", "start": 375, "end": 380, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "709c3e81-a24b-11ed-88e8-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268067", "inputs": [{"text": "ICNP 2022, the thirtieth annual version of the IEEE International Conference on Network Protocols, is the most desirable convention overlaying all elements of community protocol research, together with design, analysis, specification, verification, implementation, and performance. ICNP 2022 may be held in Lexington, Kentucky, USA among October 30 and November 2, 2022. The workshops may be hung on the thirtieth of October and the primary convention will take location at the thirty first October via second November."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "ICNP", "start": 0, "end": 4, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "709c8c36-a24b-11ed-898c-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "2022", "start": 5, "end": 9, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "709cc94d-a24b-11ed-a495-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "annual", "start": 25, "end": 31, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "709cfe40-a24b-11ed-95c4-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "ICNP", "start": 282, "end": 286, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "709d4bd7-a24b-11ed-9311-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "2022", "start": 287, "end": 291, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "709da0be-a24b-11ed-a30e-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Lexington", "start": 307, "end": 316, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "709dda6e-a24b-11ed-a73e-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Kentucky", "start": 318, "end": 326, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "709e08d8-a24b-11ed-b355-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "USA", "start": 328, "end": 331, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "709e4314-a24b-11ed-b10d-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "October 30", "start": 338, "end": 348, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "709e6b16-a24b-11ed-9399-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "November 2, 2022", "start": 353, "end": 369, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "709eb39f-a24b-11ed-adf0-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "the thirtieth of", "start": 400, "end": 416, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "709efada-a24b-11ed-abde-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "the thirty first October", "start": 474, "end": 498, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "709f21c5-a24b-11ed-b509-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "second November", "start": 503, "end": 518, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "709f497d-a24b-11ed-acdb-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268068", "inputs": [{"text": "It is obvious that the ultimate cause of the accident was a distracted diver. Legally, he was responsible for the car and could have avoided the accident. And yet, Uber is also to blame. They must have known that the current technology has its limits and you cannot expect a barely paid driver to watch over an experimental car without risking that that person grows complacent. It should be investigated if Uber did anything to ensure that their drivers were monitoring their “driverless” cars in a responsible manner."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "Uber", "start": 164, "end": 168, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "709f9c73-a24b-11ed-a401-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Uber", "start": 408, "end": 412, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "709fd690-a24b-11ed-bdc4-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}, {"key": "text1675268069", "inputs": [{"text": "Translogic 159: V2X Demonstrations at ITS World Congress: Vehicle-To-Infrastructure Communication Could Lead To Smarter, Safer Roadways - A few years ago, the hot term in car connectivity was V2V, or vehicle-to-vehicle communication. Now, another techy abbreviation has taken hold: V2X, or vehicle-to-anything-you-can-imagine. We head to the ITS World Congress in Detroit Michigan to see how the cars of the future will communicate with each other, and the world around them, with demonstrations from Honda, GM and NXP."}], "outputs": [{"annotations": [{"comment": null, "quote": "A few years ago", "start": 138, "end": 153, "label_custom_id": "DATE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf50", "label_text": "DATE", "uuid": "70a02ae7-a24b-11ed-8144-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Detroit", "start": 364, "end": 371, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "70a07884-a24b-11ed-82a4-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Michigan", "start": 372, "end": 380, "label_custom_id": "GPE", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf64", "label_text": "GPE", "uuid": "70a0c627-a24b-11ed-9d1e-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "Honda", "start": 501, "end": 506, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70a10769-a24b-11ed-82d8-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "GM", "start": 508, "end": 510, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70a141a3-a24b-11ed-a011-28d0ea216d6b"}, {"comment": null, "quote": "NXP", "start": 515, "end": 518, "label_custom_id": "ORGANIZATION", "label_id": "63da8e01a773f0dc079cbf6c", "label_text": "ORGANIZATION", "uuid": "70a1833a-a24b-11ed-a539-28d0ea216d6b"}]}]}]